- id: 401
  question: "The command to display the current directory is ___"
  answer: "pwd"
  incorrect:
    - ls
    - cd
    - whoami
    - date
- id: 402
  question: "To list all files including hidden ones, run ___ -la"
  answer: "ls"
  incorrect:
    - cat
    - pwd
    - rm
    - du
- id: 403
  question: "Change directory to /tmp using ___ /tmp"
  answer: "cd"
  incorrect:
    - pwd
    - ls
    - touch
    - mkdir
- id: 404
  question: "Create an empty file named test.txt with ___ test.txt"
  answer: "touch"
  incorrect:
    - cat
    - echo
    - cp
    - mkdir
- id: 405
  question: "Display the contents of file.txt on the terminal with ___ file.txt"
  answer: "cat"
  incorrect:
    - less
    - echo
    - rm
    - mv
- id: 406
  question: "Remove the file old.log using ___ old.log"
  answer: "rm"
  incorrect:
    - mv
    - cat
    - less
    - cp
- id: 407
  question: "Create directory docs with ___ docs"
  answer: "mkdir"
  incorrect:
    - rmdir
    - touch
    - cd
    - ls
- id: 408
  question: "Move file.txt to /tmp/ with ___ file.txt /tmp/"
  answer: "mv"
  incorrect:
    - cp
    - rm
    - touch
    - cat
- id: 409
  question: "Copy file.txt to file.bak using ___ file.txt file.bak"
  answer: "cp"
  incorrect:
    - mv
    - rm
    - cat
    - ln
- id: 410
  question: "Search for the string 'root' in passwd with ___ root /etc/passwd"
  answer: "grep"
  incorrect:
    - cat
    - find
    - cut
    - awk
- id: 411
  question: "Show running processes with ___"
  answer: "ps"
  incorrect:
    - top
    - who
    - id
    - kill
- id: 412
  question: "Display disk usage in human readable form with ___ -h"
  answer: "du"
  incorrect:
    - df
    - ls
    - free
    - ps
- id: 413
  question: "Show your current username with ___"
  answer: "whoami"
  incorrect:
    - id
    - pwd
    - echo
    - groups
- id: 414
  question: "Print the current date and time with ___"
  answer: "date"
  incorrect:
    - cal
    - time
    - clock
    - uptime
- id: 415
  question: "Shut down the system immediately with ___ now"
  answer: "shutdown"
  incorrect:
    - reboot
    - halt
    - poweroff
    - init
